<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regional level on Climate Tools</title>
    <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tags/regional-level/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regional level on Climate Tools</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:04 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tags/regional-level/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Delaware Environmental Monitoring Sites</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool59.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool59.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: DEMAC, Delaware Geological Survey, and University of Delaware</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AdaptVA: Sea Level Rise Projection Viewer</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool1.1/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VIMS_CCRM
Summary: The AdaptVA Sea Level Rise Projection Viewer uses an interactive map to display sea level rise projections for coastal Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AdaptVA: Tidewatch Map</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool1.2/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VIMS_CCRM
Summary: The AdaptVA Tidewatch Map uses an interactive map to display coastal flooding in Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Smart Farming: Apple Stage / Freeze Damage Probability</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.5/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Cornell University_College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Summary: Part of the Climate Smart Farming toolkit, the Apple Stage/Freeze Probability Tool predicts the potential freeze damage for 3 varieties of apple crops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Smart Farming: Grape Hardiness &amp; Freeze Risk</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.6/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Cornell University_College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Summary: Part of the Climate Smart Farming toolkit, the Grape Freeze Risk Tool predicts the potential freeze damage for 3 varieties of grapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Smart Farming: Growing Degree Day Calculator</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.2/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Cornell University_College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Summary: Part of the Climate Smart Farming toolkit, the Growing Degree Day Calculator calculates and plots observed and predicted growing degree days for a given location during a growing season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Smart Farming: Water Deficit Calculator</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.3/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Cornell University_College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Summary: Part of the Climate Smart Farming toolkit, the Water Deficit Calculator estimates soil water content within a crop&amp;rsquo;s effective root zone to predict potential water deficits and associated plant stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Smart Farming: Winter Cover Crop Planting Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool39.4/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Cornell University_College of Agriculture and Life Sciences
Summary: Part of the Climate Smart Farming toolkit, the Winter Cover Crop Planting Scheduler calculates the probability that specific cover crops reach important levels of growth by the end of the growing season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Resilient Water Utilities: Resilient Strategies Guide for Water Utilities</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool8.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool8.3/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: EPA
Summary: Part of the Creating Resilient Water Utilities Tool (CRWU), the Resilient Strategies Guide is a beginner resource for water utilities working on a preliminary identification of adaptation strategies specific to their needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eastern Virginia Coastal Resilience (ESVA Coastal Resilience)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool10.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool10.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: NOAA, and TNC
Summary: The Virginia Eastern Shore Coastal Resilience tool is an interactive mapping tool that allows users to visualize potential social, economic, and environmental impacts of sea level rise and storm surge and identify areas for nature-based solutions to enhance resilience and reduce risks where possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hampton Roads Geospatial Exchange Online: Hampton Roads Resilience Projects Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool2.2/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: HRPDC, HRSD, and HRTPO
Summary: Part of the Hampton Roads Geospatial Exchange Online portal, this tool provides summary graphics and an interactive map to view current and proposed projects to improve resilience to flooding and coastal hazards in Hampton Roads, VA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hampton Roads Geospatial Exchange Online: Hampton Roads Sea Level Rise Planning Scenarios (Raster)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool2.1/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: HRPDC, HRSD, and HRTPO
Summary: Part of Hampton Roads Geospatial Exchange Online, the Hampton Roads Sea Level Rise Planning Scenarios uses an interactive map to display sea level rise projections for Hampton Roads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know Your Zone</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool11.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool11.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VDEM
Summary: The Know Your Zone tool is an interactive mapping tool that allows residents of coastal Virginia to determine their evacuation zone for hurricanes and severe storms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARISA Climate Data Portal: Climate Data for the Mid-Atlantic Region</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool13.1/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: NOAA, and MARISA
Summary: Climate Data for the Mid-Atlantic Region contains a list and overview of climate data products in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARISA Climate Data Portal: Interactive Map for the MARISA Region</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool13.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool13.2/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: NOAA, and MARISA
Summary: The Interactive Map for the MARISA region is an interactive web map that enables users to view real time climate data for the MARISA region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARISA Climate Impacts Summary and Outlook Reports</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool20.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool20.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: MARISA
Summary: The MARISA Climate Impacts Summary and Outlook Reports are a quarterly series summarizing seasonal weather and climate trends and forecasts for the Chesapeake Bay Watershed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Atlantic Ocean Data Tool</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool40.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool40.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: MARCO
Summary: The Mid-Atlantic Ocean Data Portal is a resource center consisting of an interactive map, data layers, case studies, and collaborative tools that allows users to explore and share visualizations of coastal and societal resources from New York to Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Conservation Planning Atlas</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool43.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool43.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: Conservation Biology Institute
Summary: The Northeast Conservation Planning Atlas (CPA) is an online mapping platform where users can view, retrieve, and analyze spatial data for conservation planning in the Northeast US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operational Forecast System: Chesapeake Bay Operational Forecast System (CBOFS)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool3.1/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: NOAA
Summary: The Chesapeake Bay Operational Forecast System (CBOFS) tool is a data viewer that provides real time forecasts of oceanographic conditions in the Chesapeake Bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operational Forecast System: Delaware Bay Operational Forecast System (DBOFS)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool3.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool3.2/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: NOAA, and Rutgers University_Regional Ocean Modeling System
Summary: The Delaware Bay Operational Forecast System (DBOFS) tool is a data viewer that provides real time forecasts of oceanographic conditions in the Delaware Bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoreline Assessment Mapper</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool19.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool19.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VIMS_CCRM
Summary: The Shoreline Assessment Mapper is an interactive map that displays a variety of shoreline data for the coastal zone of Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submerged Aquatic Vegetation (SAV) in the Chesapeake Bay</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool38.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool38.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VIMS
Summary: The Submerged Aquatic Vegetation (SAV) in Chesapeake Bay tool provides access to recent and historical SAV monitoring data from the Virginia Institute of Marine Science SAV program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USGS Geo Data Portal (GDP)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool7.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: USGS
Summary: The USGS Geo Data Portal (GDP) is designed for advanced users looking to access meteorological, climate, and urban growth data at national and regional scales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Coastal Geospatial and Educational Mapping System (GEMS)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool41.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool41.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: VDEQ
Summary: The Virginia Coastal Geospatial and Educational Mapping System (Coastal GEMS) is an interactive map and inventory of coastal resource data and conservation planning tools for Virginia’s coastal zone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Wetland Condition Assessment Tool (WetCAT)</title>
      <link>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cbtooltest.marisa.psu.edu/tools/page-tool4.0/</guid>
      <description>Developed By: CCRM, and VDEQ
Summary: The Virginia Wetland Condition Assessment Tool (WetCAT) is an interactive map that assesses wetland capacity to perform ecosystem services and provides the tools to conduct analyses useful for wetland restoration efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
